U.S. National Mediation Board Agreements 5806
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Crown Air/Dorado Wings-- Pilots, 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Executive Jet Aviation, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Florida Airlines, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Golden West Airlines, Inc. Pilots, 1978-1981 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Markair -- Flt, Deck Crew Members (Markair, formerly Alaska Int'l. Air), 1991 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Metroflight Airlines, Inc. Pilots, 1981-1985 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Midstate Airlines Pilots, 1982-1984 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Midways Airlines -- Pilots, 1986-1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Pacific Southwest Airlines Pilots, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- A 9450, 1976-1978 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico International Airlines, Inc. Pilots, 1980-1983 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Rocky Mountain-Airways - Pilots, 1983-1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Ross Aviation, Inc. Pilots, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Scenic Air Lines Pilots, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Suburban Airlines, Inc. Pilots, 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Viking International Pilots, 1983-1985 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- American, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Eastern, 1980-1986 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Northwest R+T, 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- United, 1980-1983 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Ozark, 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Piedmont (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Aeronautical Radio, Inc. Radio and Teletype Operators, 1977-1979 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Air India Teletype Operators, 1980-1983 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Avianca, Inc. Teletype, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- British Overseas Airways Corp. Teletype Operators, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Iberia Airlines Teletype Operators, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Kim Royal Dutch Airlines Teletype Operators, 1972-1975 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Lufthansa German Airlines Teletype (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Olympic Airways, Inc. Radionand Teletype Operators, 1972-1975 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Swissair Swiss Air Transport Co., Ltd. Teletype Operators, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- American, 1980-1982 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Pan Am. - Service Supply Clerks - Basic Agreement including Guam - System Agreement, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- Pan American - Service Supply Clerks ASD/ETR, 1981-1987 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Ozark, 1982-1985 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Piedmont, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Southwest Airlines - Stock and Store, 1983-1989 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Alaska Airlines, Inc., 1981-1984 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- Capitol Air Sales, Inc. Stock Clerks, 1978-1981 (Box 60, Folder 32)
- Flying Tiger Airlines Stock Clerks, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 33)
- World Airways, 1982-1985 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- Aerocondor Airlines Stock Clerks, 1980-1982 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- Aerovias Nacionales De Columbia (Avianca) S.A., 1975 (Box 60, Folder 36)
- Alitaria Air Lines Stocks and Stores, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 37)
- British (Overseas) Airways Stock and Stores, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- El Al Israel Airlines Storekeepers, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 39)
- Klm Royal Dutch Airlines Stock Clerks, 1981-1984 (Box 60, Folder 40)
- A 9448, 1976-1979 (Box 60, Folder 41)
- Qantas Airways Stocks, 1976-1979 (Box 60, Folder 42)
- Swissair Swiss Air Transport Co., Ltd. Stock Clerks, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 43)
- Taca Stores, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 44)
- Varig Airlines Stocks, 1981-1984 (Box 60, Folder 45)
- Air California -- Stock Clerks, 1981-1985 (Box 60, Folder 46)
- Executive Jet Aviation Stock Clerks, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 47)
- Teamsters Local 2707, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 48)
- American, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Trans World Airlines Flight Engineers, 1981-1983 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Pan American Flight Engineers (#3 1977) (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Reeve Aleutian Airways, Inc. Flight Engineers, 1977-1980 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Airlift (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Flying Tiger, 1979-1980 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Capital International, 1979-1982 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Trans International, 1981-1984 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- World Airways, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Northwest - Anchorage, AK. Flight Kitchen, 1982-1985 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Northwest - Flight Kitchen, 1982-1985 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Pan American Commissary Employees - Cape Kennedy, 1981-1984 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Pan American Commissary Em'ees - New York Area, 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. Dining Service, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- United, 1982-1986 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- El Al Israel Airlines Commissary Agents, 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Swissair Swiss Air Transport Co., Ltd. Kitchen, Commissary em'ees, 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Varig Airlines Commissary, 1981-1984 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Sky Chefs Commissary Em'ees, 1985-1988 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Capital International, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Trans International, 1974-1976 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Eastern, 1981-1984 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Northwest - Meteorologists, 1980-1983 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Trans World (TWA) Meteorologists, 1977-1979 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- United - Meteorologist, 1982-1985 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- American - Guards, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Instructors - Ground School and Simulator Technicians - American Airlines, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Continental - Guards, 1976-1978 (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Continental -- Grnd. Instructors, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 29)
- Eastern Air Lines - Drivers, 1983-1985 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Eastern - Flight Operations Ground School Instructors, 1979-1982 (Box 61, Folder 31)
- Eastern Guards, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Eastern Airlines Medical Services Personnel, 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Eastern Nurses, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 34)
- Security Officers Eastern Air Lines, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 35)
- Eastern Airlines Technical /Regional Instructors, 1979-1982 (Box 61, Folder 36)
- Northwest: Plant Protection Men, 1981-1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Northwest: Plant Protection Men, 1981-1985 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. Instructor, Prod. Planner, Tech. Manual Writer, Ser. Analyst, Simulator Tech., 1982-1985 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Pan Am.-- Bldg. Maint. Engineers, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Pan Am. - Flt. Nst. (Pt. of Pilots), 1982-1985 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Pan American Flt. Sim. Tech. and Flt. Sim. Eng., 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Pan American Flight Specialists and Balloon Watchmen, 1977-1980 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Pan American Medical and Environmental Technicians, 1976-1979 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Pan American Medical Corpsmen - Occupational Medicine and Environmental, 1979-1982 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Pan American Airlines Nurses (Airline Operations), 1978 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Pan. Am.--Nurses, Occupational Medicine Kennedy Space Center (Merritt Island), 1976-1979 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Pan American Security Policemen (ASD/ETR), 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Pan American Senior Port Stewards, 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Pan American Senior Port Stewards, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Pan American Airlines Operations Training Instructors (Flight Engineer Instructors), 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Trans World Airlines Cargo, Commissary + Stock, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. Guards, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- United Airlines Flight Simulator Operators, 1976-1986 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- United - Guards, 1984-1987 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- United Ramps + Stores, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- USAIR -- Flt. Simulators, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Instructors Western Air Lines, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Frontier Airlines, Inc. Engineers and Related, 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Supervisors of Mechanical Personnel Republic Airlines, 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Alaskas Airlines Ramp Servicemen, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Security '76 Inc. Security Employees, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Flying Tiger Line - Grnd. Inst., 1983-1987 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Flying Tiger Line Inc. Plant Protection Officers, 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Flying Tiger Line Inc. Ramp Servicemen and Related Employees, 1979-1982 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Aerolineas Argentinas Commission Employees, 1976-1978 (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Aeromexico - (Aeronaves De Mexico Sales Representatives Employees, 1978-1980 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Aero Peru, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Altaria Air Lines Cargo Agents, Commissary Agents, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Altaria Air Lines Traffic Representatives, 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Avianca, Inc. Sales Representatives, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 35)
- British Overseas Airways Cargo, Station, and Baggage, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 36)
- British Overseas Airways - Officers and Supervisors, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 37)
- British Overseas Airways Port Stewards, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 38)
- British Airways Technical Officer (Computer Technician), 1975 (Box 62, Folder 39)
- British West Indian Airways Maintenance Supervisors, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 40)
- British West Indian Airways Reservation and Station Employees, 1974-1977 (Box 62, Folder 41)
- El Al Israel Airlines Cargo and Passenger Agens, and Passenger Officers, 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 42)
- Irish International Airlines Cargo Agents, Station Agents, 1981-1984 (Box 62, Folder 43)
- KLM Royal Dutch Airlines - Station; Cargo; Pass. Ser., + Drivers, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 44)
- Lineas Aereas, 1977-1980 (Box 62, Folder 45)
- Qantas Airways Cargo Agents, 1976-1979 (Box 62, Folder 46)
- Sabena--Switchboard Operators, Chauffeurs, warehousemen, Agents, Cargo Agents and Traffic Agents, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 47)
- Scandinavian Airlines System Passenger Ser., Operations, Tech. Forwarding Cargo Ser., Cargo Reservations, and Cargo Fit. Mant., 1978- 1981 (Box 62, Folder 48)
- Swissair Swiss Air Transport Co., Ltd. Cargo, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 49)
- Trans Mediterranean Airways Cargo Agents, Cargo Clerks, and Driver, 1976-1982 (Box 62, Folder 50)
- Varig Airlines - Traffic Agents, Cargo Agents, 1984-1988 (Box 62, Folder 51)
- Shamrock Air Lines Porters, 1976-1979 (Box 62, Folder 52)
- Airline Aerospace and Allied Employees, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 53)
- Pacific Southwest Airlines Schedulers, 1983-1985 (Box 62, Folder 54)
- Western Airlines, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- World Airways Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- World Airways Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- USAir, 1982-1984 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Western Air Lines, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Western Air Lines, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- World Airways, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- World Airways, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- World Airways, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- United Air Lines, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Company, 1944-1962 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Yardmasters, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Various Agreements (Box 63, Folder 13)
- A-H, 1981-1987 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- K-N (1), 1981-1987 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- K-N (2), 1981-1987 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Ozark Airlines, 1981-1985 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Ozark Lines Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Ozark Air Lines, Inc., 1983 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- P-R, 1979-1987 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- 'P', 1979-1982 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- T-S, 1977-1987 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- T-S, 1977-1987 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Texas International Airlines, Inc., 1978-1983 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- TWA, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- United Air Lines, Inc., 1979-1983 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1958-1964 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Extra Agreements and Contracts, 1977-1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- 'A', 1980-1983 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- 'A', 1977-1980 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Airlift International, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- American Airlines, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Air Canada, Airlift International, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- American Airlines, Inc., 1977 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Aloha Airlines, Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- British Airways, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Combs Airways, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- The Flying Tiger Line Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Continental Airlines + The Flying Tiger Line Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Air Line Pilots, 1979-1982 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Eastern Air Lines, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Frontier Air Lines, 1980-1983 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Norfolk, 1965-1969 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- The Virginian Railway Company + The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company, 1949-1954 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- 'A', 1972-1983 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- 'L', 1946-1981 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Chicago Union Station Company, 1946-1981 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Chicago Companies, 1953-1977 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- The Railway Patrolmen's International Union, 1946-1955 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Illinois Central Railroad Company + Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad, 1942-1943 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Railway Patrolmen's International Union, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Braniff Airways, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Yardmasters, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Illinois Central Railroad Company, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Yardmasters, 1947-1974 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- 'N', 1972 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Yardmasters, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Southern Pacific Company, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Misc., 1950 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- The Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1967-1970 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies 'M', 1946 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Railroad Companies 'C', 1946-1949 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- 'T' Railroad Companies, 1941-1952 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- National Council of Railroad Patrolmen, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1949-1956 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1938-1962 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1940-1979 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Maine Central Railroad Company, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- New York Central Railroad, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Railroad Companies 'M', 1928-1974 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Various Agreements (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Various Agreements (Box 67, Folder 19)
- The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1926-1937 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- 'C' Railroad Companies, 1967-1969 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway and Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Companies, 1923-1965 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1940-1973 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1923-1980 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Company, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1928-1963 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- The Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company, 1966-1973 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1939-1971 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- The Order of Railway Conductors and Trainmen, 1944-1957 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Dining Car Employees, 1950-1976 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1919-1967 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1937-1967 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company and Chicago Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company, 1937-1957 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1945-1975 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- 'G' Railway Companies, 1921-1968 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- The Pennsylvania - New York Central Transportation Company, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Houston Belt and Terminal RR and Yardmasters, 1930-1975 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers Express and Station Employees, 1937-1964 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Locomotive Engineers, 1924-1958 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1945-1963 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1938-1952 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1958-1967 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- American Railway Supervisors, 1947-1950 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company, 1944 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Texas and Pacific Railway Company, 1928-1957 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- The Pullman Company + The Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1945-1955 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- The Order of Telegraphers, 1946-1956 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Brotherhood of Railroad System, 1938-1947 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen + Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1943-1976 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- The Order of Railroad Telegraphers + Engineers, 1929-1949 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad + Fort Worth and Denver City Railway Company, 1940-1942 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- The Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company, 1949-1953 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1940-1958 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Railroad Companies 'C', 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- The Virginian Railway Company, 1942-1950 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Duluth Missabe and Iron Range Railway Company, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- 'M-N' Railway Companies, 1940-1953 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Firemen, Oilers, Helpers Roundhouse and Railway Shop Laborers, 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1955-1956 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- American Train Dispatchers' Association + Conductors Trainmen and Yardmen, 1924-1927 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Machinists, Boilermakers, Blacksmiths, Sheet Metal Workers etc., 1936-1937 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen + Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1947-1955 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- The Western Pacific Railroad Company + Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1940-1968 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, 1939-1973 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railway, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1944-1974 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- (BRT), 1938-1957 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, 1951-1973 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- (Firemen), 1948-1953 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Southern Pacific Company, 1936-1937 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Colorado Railway Cos. + Locomotive Engineers, 1929-1951 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1927-1947 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- 'D' Railroad Companies, 1927-1946 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- The Atchison and Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1966-1970 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Co. + Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co., 1936-1950 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks etc., 1946-1980 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Railway Companies (A-C), 1942-1954 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Conductors and Brakemen, 1929-1966 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- American Federation of Labor, 1956-1979 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Locomotive Firemen and Engineermen, 1925-1954 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Co., 1946-1973 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Co., 1949 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1976 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- EJ+E revised (12/11/81) pages, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corp., 1954-1961 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Various Railroad Corp., 1982 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Central Vermont Railway, Inc., 1976 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Enginemen, Firemen, Engineers, 1919-1956 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Central of Georgia Railway Company, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous, 1937-1966 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- 'B' Railroad Companies, 1927-1960 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company + Central Vermont Railway, Inc., 1951-1972 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company + The Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railway, 1946-1971 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1961-1972 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Minneapolis St Paul, and Sault St. Marie Railroad Company, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Railroad Companies (I-L), 1945-1971 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- 'E' Railroad Company, 1955-1971 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Misc., 1939-1978 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- 'G' Railroad Companies, 1942-1955 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Order of Telegraphers + Maintenance of Way Employees + Railroad Companies 'G', 1936-1971 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Co. + Great Northern Railway Company, 1938-1971 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Firemen, Clerks, The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Co. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1947-1961 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Engineers, 1930-1948 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Lake Terminal Railroad Company + 'C' Railroad Companies, 1945-1957 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- 'P-R' Railroad Companies, 1957-1971 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous, 1928-1954 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Conductors and Brakemen + Southern Pacific Company + 'C' Railway Company, 1945-1950 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Brotherhoods, 1972-1978 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company + Hudson and Manhattan Railroad Company + Union Pacific, 1945-1965 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Various Railway Companies, 1924-1943 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Steamship Clerks + Yardmasters, 1962-1974 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- BRT, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen + Brhd. Of Locomotive Engineers, 1927-1957 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Chicago, Pennsylvania Railroad Company, American Railway Supervisor's Association, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees + Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1958 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Engineers, 1949 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Locomotive Engineers + Firemen and Conductors, 1931-1951 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1942-1980 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- (W) Railroad Companies, 1922-1932 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way + Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, 1955-1973 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Misc., 1940-1953 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- (D) Railway Companies, 1936-1940 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- 'C' Railroad Companies, 1931-1979 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Firemen + Engineers, 1925-1954 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Agreements - Not Booked, 1952-1988 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Trainmen and Yardmen, 1955-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1941-1950 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen + Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, 1948-1973 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad, Illinois Central Railroad + Switchmen, Firemen, 1938-1966 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers + (B) Railroad Companies, 1939-1952 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Maintenance of Way + Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1940-1944 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers + Maintenance of Way Employees, 1937-1963 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company + The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railway Company, 1962-1974 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- 'C' Railroad Companies, 1956-1959 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Wabash Railroad + Peoria and Pekia Union Railway Co. + Detroit Toledo and Ironton Railroad Co., 1919-1947 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Southern Railway, 1949-1973 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Brhd. Of Maintenance of Way + Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1922-1951 (Box 76, Folder 13)